tcadmin.com 2007-12-28

# TCADMIN - The Game Hosting Control Panel

This Privacy Policy covers Balance Server’s treatment of personally identifiable information that Balance Servers collects when you are on the TCAdmin.com site, and when you use Balance Servers or TCAdmin services. This policy also covers Balance Servers' treatment of any personally identifiable information that Balance Servers’s business partners share with us. 

## Information Collection and Use

  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Balance Servers does not own or control, or to people that Balance Servers does not employ or manage.
  * Balance Servers collects personally identifiable information when you register for a TCAdmin account, when you use certain TCAdmin products or services and when you visit TCAdmin.com pages.
  * When you register with Balance Servers, we ask for your name, email address, zip code, and phone number. Once you register with Balance Servers and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
  * Balance Servers also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, TCAdmin cookie information and the page you requested.
  * Balance Servers uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products.   

##   
Information Sharing and Disclosure 

  * Balance Servers will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. 
  * Balance Servers will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 
    * We have your consent to share the information; 
    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; 
    * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Ipswich Shellfish to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.); 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or We find that your actions on our web sites violate the Balance Servers / TCAdmin terms of service agreement, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.  

##   
Cookies  

  * Balance Servers may set and access Balance Servers or TCAdmin cookies on your computer, but only at your request. 
  * You may request deletion of your Balance Servers / TCAdmin account by sending an email to support@tcadmin.com 
  * Your Balance Servers / TCAdmin Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. 

##   
Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * Balance Servers may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
